https://www.ngex.com/info/privacy.htm

NigeriaExchange
More...
Privacy Statement For NigeriaExchange (NgEX.com)
NGEX, LLC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: "www.NigeriaExchange.com or www.ngex.com." This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also use to gather broad demographic information.
Our site may use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly and to deliver content specific to your interests.
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information may also be used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice-opt-out section below.
As a general rule, NigeriaExchnage.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Please see the Terms of Use Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared.
This site contains links to other sites. NigeriaExchange.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.
Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.
We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners.
The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when
necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at out site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.
We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our site.
These ads may contain cookies.
While we use cookies in other parts of our Web Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Some customer data may be shared with the advertising companies on an aggregate basis.
Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users.
Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Supplementation Information
This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties.
Choice/Opt-Out
Out site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
You can send email to remove@ngex.com
Correct/Update
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.
email
update@ngex.com
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
NigeriaExchange.com,LLC
Privacy@ngex.com
Mail us
with questions or comments about this web site.
© 1997 - 1999 NgEX!. All rights reserved .
